Six Rogue Filmmakers Explore The Hidden Side Of Everything
Freakonomics is a documentary film directed by Alex Gibney.
Some of the world's most innovative documentary filmmakers
will explore the hidden side of everything.
Blake, played by Zoe Sloane.
High School Girl, played by Jade Viggiano.
Mercedes, played by Amancaya Aguilar.
Deshawn, played by Kahiry Bess.
Student, played by Alisha Nagarsheth.
High School Girl, played by Alyssa Wheeldon.
Freakonomics: The Movie is a 2010 American documentary film based on the 2005 nonfiction book
Freakonomics: A Rogue Economist Explores the Hidden Side of Everything written by economist Steven D.
Levitt and writer Stephen J.
The film premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival in April 2010,
and had a theatrical release later that year.
On Rotten Tomatoes, the film has an approval rating of
66% based on reviews from 64 critics.
The film explores themes of high school,
corruption, experiment, cheating, limousine.